souqmobi.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - SouqMobi

At SouqMobi we are devoted to protecting and maintaining the privacy of our users and visitors. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you give to us, or that we gather from you whilst you visit our site.   
We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

**Information We Collect**  
In operational and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.

  * Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you fill the form.

  * Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

**Use of Cookies**  
We may use cookies where proper to gather information about your computer fin order to assist us in improving our website.   
We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computers hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever   
You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish.  Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  Such cookies would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

**Use of Your Information**  
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.  In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  * To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.

  * To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you.

  * To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.

Where your approval has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you.  Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.

 **Storing Your Personal Data**  
In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is treated stored securely.  
Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, Sending such information is entirely at your own risk. 

**Disclosing Your Information**  
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  * In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.

  * Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.

  * To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.

**Third Party Links**  
On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data. 

**Access to Information**  
You have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. 

**Contacting Us**  
Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at info@souqmobi.com
